

# MAARTEN HORMES

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER IN TRAINING

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

E-mail: maarten.hormes@gmail.com Phone number: +31 6 18687280

Address: Karel Doormanstraat 3c 6045EA Roermond

Date of birth: 27-01- 2000



LinkedIn



GitHub link



Portfolio site

### **ABOUT ME**

Hello there, I am a full stack software engineer to be. Currently studying at Fontys ICT on my way to a bachelors degree. Next to that, I'm working as a full stack web developer at Limax B.V.

I've chosen software engineering, because I've been experimenting with writing software since high school. After starting my studies, this interest has turned into a hobby and personal need to understand, know more and get better at what I like doing.

I am a social person, a team player, goal oriented and very structured. I like to get things done, properly! Structure makes a developers life easier, thats why I love it so much. I am always open to converse and share views in order to find the most suitable solution/approach for each situation.

Although I only have 3 years of experience under my belt, I am able to understand complex concepts due to my habit of always wanting to know more and my willingness to have a open conversation about a wide range of topics (both IT and non-IT related).

#### **EDUCATION**

2020 - present

Fontys ICT & software engineering, Feb 2023 - present English stream, Eindhoven

**Graduated HAVO** 

2012-2018

6 Atheneum, Natuur & Techniek

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Limax B.V., Horst (Side-job)

Junior software engineer

• Continued on the full stack development of the Flowcontrol system

Limax B.V., Horst (Internship)

Aug 2022 - Jan 2023

Software engineer intern

• Researched and created a security implementation for the Flowcontrol system

DEYO Huiswerkbegeleiding, Roermond (Side-Job)

Apr 2022 - Feb 2023

• Tutored in Dutch and math.

#### LANGUAGES

Dutch Native Language English Fluent

German Average

## HOBBY'S

Football/Sports

Music (technical side of music as well as playing the guitar/singing)

Software development

Online media (YouTube/Twitch)

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### Developed in:

- C#
- Java (Spring)
- JavaScript (React.js / Vue.js)

#### Worked with:

- Docker
- Keycloak
- Postman
- Sonarqube
- JIRA
- TailwindCSS
- IntelliJ
- Visual Studio (Code)

## SOFT SKILLS

#### Professional skills:

- Structured
- Orderly
- Result driven
- Team player

#### Personal skills:

- Passionate
- Communicative
- Independent